Kaymenaki Eirini

- > UI/UX Designer
- > Adobe Applications Trainer

Areas of expertise:

- > Web and UI Design
- > SEO
- > Adobe CC Expert / AEM Mobile
- > Wireframes, Prototyping

OBJECTIVE

Ambitious, fast-moving, and visionary UI/UX Designer with over 10 years experience in design and 3 years experience in A/B testing and software testing, universal design, usability and accessibility, data visualization, web development and user-centred systems design.

Enthusiastic about improving the design of interactive systems and services, and exploring the journey to achieve the desirable result through a human-centred approach.

EXPERIENCE

September 2017 – present

Yorkshire Building Society Group - Leeds, UK

UI/UX Designer / Lead Technical SEO Developer

- > Producing wireframes, design assets for the YBS website and mobile
- > Developing and publishing content using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and XML for the YBS Group websites
- Contributing to multiple projects on re-designing and migrating content to Oracle WebCenter Sites CMS for YBS, CBS and Accord brands
- > Planning and running A/B tests
- > Designing User Personas and User Flows
- > Lead technical SEO developer
- > Data analysis and working with Clicktale to report, track and resolve issues
- Managing and testing the Oracle WebCenter Sites CMS after code deployments and reporting product defects/issues to key stakeholders
- > Working closely with the in-house UX and back-end teams on crafting customers online experience
- > Liaising with developers and testing support team on the development process to resolve issues in a timely fashion
- > Agile working-stand up meetings and use of scrum board for sprints
- > Participating in the development process from definition, through design, build, test, release, and maintenance
- > Leading and training the email content design team and ensuring content pages are consistent and accurately created
- > Training and supporting staff on how to use Adobe applications for web design and development
- > Researching innovative creative and development ideas for testing and implementation

September 2015 - August 2017

Foster + Partners - London, UK

Digital Design Specialist / Adobe Applications Trainer

Delivered training and provided support for Adobe applications and Adobe's Experience Manager (AEM) CMS for the practice globally

- Contributed to the design and development of the company's showcase mobile app using AEM CMS
- > Updated and maintained application and website content using AEM CMS
- Organised and facilitated brainstorming sessions with the product team and produced highly polished user interfaces based on user feedback and product vision for the company and its showcase mobile app
- > Worked with Partners and the Creative & Development team on creating wireframes, user flows, clickable mockups for the company's mobile app
- > Worked alongside the Product Design team and designed app homepages, content spots, static pages and category banners
- > Worked as part of the product team to modernize the company website.

July 2012 – July 2015

Think + Print - Athens, Greece

Creative Director

- > Design and production of graphics for proposals and diagrams
- > Directing art projects, setting standards and interpreting briefs
- > Project management, coordinating artwork, print and delivery
- > Quality assurance of external service providers
- Design and production of high-quality printed and web-based brochures, newsletters, advertisements, and marketing material for exhibitions and conferences
- > Standards compliance for branded materials

March 2006 - December 2012

Village roadshow operation - Athens, Greece

Junior Graphic designer

- > Creation of print media: newsletters, publications, covers, posters, brochures, cd/dvd covers using Indesign, Photoshop and Illustrator
- > Concept design create visual themes for Global conferences, client workshops, retreats using Indesign, Photoshop and Illustrator
- > Web-design design and development of both internet and intranet sites on demand Lotus Notes/html

EDUCATION

September 2017 - present

University of Edinburgh - UK

MSc Digital Media Design / HCI

September 2002 – September 2008

National Technical University of Athens - Greece

BA Graphic Design and Multimedia

LANGUAGES / SKILLS

English - Full professional proficiency

French - Basic knowledge

Greek - Native